Gustavo Honorato

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Profile

Software Engineer since 2019, with a strong foundation in IT, studying in the field since 2017.

Born in 2000, always eager to learn and improve. Adaptable and quick to learn new technologies, ensuring the best solutions for any challenge.

Experienced in Python And Golang:)

Employment History

Software Engineer - Mid Level, Mercado Livre, Remote

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Back-end solutions with Python & Flask (Blueprints) and Golang
- Front-end solutions with React
- CI/CD with Circle CI and GitHub actions and jenkins
- Observability with Datadog, Kibana and New Relic
- E2E, integration and unit tests
- TDD
- Gitflow
- Database: Mysql

Software Engineer - Mid Level, Stone, Pagar.me, Remote

JULY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

- Back-end solutions with Python & FastApi and Node & NestJS.
- GCP (Cloud run, Cloud functions, Pub-sub, Storage)
- CI/CD with Circle CI and GitHub actions
- E2E, integration and unit tests using pytest
- TDD
- Trunk Based Development
- Database: PostgreSQL and Firestore

Software Engineer - Mid Level, Enforce, Remote

FEBRUARY 2022 - JULY 2022

- Back-end solutions with Python & Flask & FastApi.
- AWS (Event-Bridge)
- CI/CD with Azure DevOps
- Front-end solutions with Angular 8
- System integrations
- Integrations tests and Unit Tests using tox

Software Engineer - Entry Level, Enforce, Campinas

JANUARY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

- Back-end solutions with Python & Flask.
- RESTful API's with Swagger
- AWS (Lambda, Cloud-formation, Cloud-front, EKS, SQS, SNS, Event-Bridge)
- Kubernetes Management (Rancher)

Details

Campinas

Brasil

(+55 19) 9 7102 9973

gustavo.honoratonic@gmail.com

Links

Github

Linkedin

Skills

Python

Golang

Java

Node

Flask

FastApi

Angular

React

PostgresSQL

Mysql

Firestore

AWS

GCP

Languages

Portuguese

English

- CI/CD with Azure DevOps
- Front-end solutions with Angular 8

Internships

IT Intern, Enforce

MARCH 2019 - DECEMBER 2020

- Back-end solutions with Python & Flask and Java & Spring.
- RESTful API's with Swagger
- AWS (Lambda, Cloud-formation, SQS, SNS)
- Kubernetes Management (Rancher)
- CI/CD with Azure DevOps
- Front-end solutions with Angular 8

Education

Tecnólogo, FATEC, Campinas

JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2022

I finished my college in 2022, I had a lot of contact with theory and practice of all stages of software development

Técnico, SENAI SÃO PAULO, Campinas

JANUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

First contact I had with programming and soon I fell in love. It was two excellent years, I had a TCC that used ANDROID (JAVA) and C # to build a webservice.